Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, this is going to be Ashley Martin.
Dr. Belis Aladag: For last her cures report shows
Dr. Belis Aladag: Suboxone film.
Dr. Belis Aladag: eight milligrams twice a day.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And that was given
Dr. Belis Aladag: March. Second thing.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, there's another patient Calvin Crawford is curious, check.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Shows clonazepam on
Dr. Belis Aladag: Dr towns and then
Dr. Belis Aladag: The sub solve given to him on
Dr. Belis Aladag: Can be February 14
Dr. Belis Aladag: By Dr. Bob swing.
Dr. Belis Aladag: So I'm not sure if Calvin.
Dr. Belis Aladag: The male
Dr. Belis Aladag: Patient will be coming on first, or if Ashley, the female one will be coming on because Ashley's late and Calvin is early. Hello.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Calvin.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Yeah. Hi Calvin. How's it going,
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Good, how are you
Dr. Belis Aladag: Good. I'm Dr. Allah DAG and I'm here to help you.
Dr. Belis Aladag: With your opioid issue.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Yeah, well, Tommy. Can you tell me a little bit of about yourself like your background with that, like how you ended up with us.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah. Um, well, I haven't been getting well I started using opiates. When I was like 15 and then I started with Suboxone when I was around 1819
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Okay, so that was about 10 years ago and
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: I had a doctor who was given giving me this Suboxone and along with my other medications. He was like high interest for like eight years and then
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: I ended up switching doctors to one that was covered by medical clinical lay
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: And then she had referred me to you guys just recently. Well, I lost. I had this really great doctor with clinical lay up until December. And then I feel like they've kind of just been tossing me around here. So this doctor to that doctor and she had referred me to you guys, so
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, that's basically how I ended up here.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, okay. Um, okay. Cool. Well, hopefully we can we can hang on to and
Dr. Belis Aladag: Take care of you, like you had like a study
Dr. Belis Aladag: Sounds like so you were on it for 10 years and
Dr. Belis Aladag: last eight years, right. You were or no, you
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Like I address. Yeah. And then, yeah, it's kind of been like switching from this doctor that Dr. Past a year and a half or so.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, okay, um,
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: And I've actually been on the Methadone for like two months now.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Oh me over because I had stopped you getting the Suboxone
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: And I really don't like it. You know, I'd really like to get back on the Suboxone
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, so going from methadone or Suboxone is going to be a you know a little bit of a challenge to you aware that
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: You have to be off of the methadone, I guess, right, I mean,
Dr. Belis Aladag: Yeah so methadone.
Dr. Belis Aladag: It stays in your system for they say 48 hours, but I've had patients really have to stay clear of of all of everything for like four or five days before. So like, there needs to be a gap. Before we start you on the Suboxone
Good.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And that gap can be difficult.
Dr. Belis Aladag: We can do I can give you something.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Like quantity and patches that kind of help with the withdrawal, a little bit ease ease the irritability and like it's just a blood pressure lowering medication.
Dr. Belis Aladag: I can give you those patches and then it looks like. Are you still seeing some somebody that gives you clonazepam so I was
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Checking know that's that's what the other problem is, um,
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: I haven't been able to get my Klonopin steadily for the past like five days. And I'm really been feeling terrible not having that and then having the, you know, having to go back and forth the Methadone clinic.
Dr. Belis Aladag: I see. So who is, who is the doctor giving you your Klonopin
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Well, he stopped working for clinical a and now and
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: So it was Dr. Towns.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Uh huh.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Who gave me the last prescription for that. But I've done a clause and also for about the same time, same amount of time as a Suboxone so I've been like that for like 10 years now.
Dr. Belis Aladag: 10 years as well. Okay, and
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: It's just really hard not having it for the past
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: You know, five, six days.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Well, yeah, it's not something you really should be running out of so so the clinic, the clinic, your ad is like, sorry. There's no doctor here that can give that to you. Is that what they're saying.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, he says, uh,
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: It's really, it's really a mess. They said they sent me to a doctor in Fairfield, which is next town over and
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: I thought I've been waiting this couple weeks to meet with him. I thought he was just going to take care of everything for me. But it turns out he ended up not being able to do anything for me.
Dr. Belis Aladag: None of it.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: No and yeah i know i don't i can't believe that they're letting me just, you know, go without it like this. I've been calling them and like messaging them and doing everything I can. But I'm not getting anywhere.
Dr. Belis Aladag: That's not good.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, so here's what I think we should do. Okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: I do think if you've been on clonazepam for that long for 10 years. You can't just suddenly stop it.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Now that's like dangerous. We don't want that. You could go into withdrawal. And that's, you know, not a good thing from from benzodiazepines. Okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: You know, long term moving forward. Should you remain on it you know that's something between you and the psychiatrist taking care of you to discuss. But I think short term. I mean, you need to be covered. Yeah, um,
Dr. Belis Aladag: So, so for that.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Maybe what I can do, since you've been out for five days now. No, no.
Dr. Belis Aladag: No. So, so I can give you some to kind of hold you over until you can be seen by one of our psychiatry, yes.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Oh, good health. Okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And then establish care and, you know, tell them your history and then continue your prescription or whatever you're going to do. But yeah, I think that's important. So I'll definitely give you some to hold you up.
Dr. Belis Aladag: So I'll give you a week's worth and within that week, we'll get you connected
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Good. Okay, thank you.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And you take how much two milligrams times
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, I just take two milligrams in the morning.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay. Okay, so I'll get you that ordered
Dr. Belis Aladag: And
Dr. Belis Aladag: So have you ever had any seizures or overdose situations or
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, I had in back in like 2014 well the doctor he had been giving me an absurd amount of medications. He had me on a milligrams of Xanax and eight milligrams of Klonopin per day.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: And even then, I was taking more than what he was getting me and I was getting early appointments with him and he's on probation. Now, because of all this, like,
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: I know it's terrible. But, uh, yeah. At that time I had
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Coming off of it. But I went to a medical detox facility to, you know, reduce the amount that I was on. So I ended up just falling back down to two milligrams per day.
Dr. Belis Aladag: After that, okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Wow, okay, who was who was that doctor
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Dr Ouma in Santa Lena yes i i stopped seeing and that's he's the one that was with for like eight years. And then finally, I stopped seeing him and I found this great doctor with clinical lay, but then she moved on.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, gotcha. Okay. Um, okay, so fine. So we'll figure it out. The Klonopin thing until we can find you somebody here and then you can steadily see that person and get your prescription. So that's taken care of. Good.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Now the question of, okay, how do we move you from methadone maintenance to back to Suboxone
Dr. Belis Aladag: How much methadone or you're on right now. What's the dose.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: 80 milligrams and I haven't gone. I didn't go today. I just I slept in and ended up being too late and I knew I had this appointment. Anyway, so I figured I might be covered or
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: You know, whatever, whatever happens with it. Um, but yeah, he milligrams
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, so you're an 80 milligrams and you've been doing it for two months. So yeah, I mean,
Dr. Belis Aladag: Yeah, you're just gonna. So here's what you do you work with the clinic there the Methadone clinic.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Mom.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And you tell them the plan and you say, I want it. And the thing is the interesting part is actually um Methadone clinics. Nowadays most of them also prescribe Suboxone
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah. Yeah. Except for this one I'm going to because
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: I wasn't searching at the down. You know, I was just searching for those Suboxone but um
Dr. Belis Aladag: I see. So they don't offer it as
Dr. Belis Aladag: I see. Okay, so. Nevermind that but but just tell them the plan just say, Okay, I found a Suboxone provider. So I need to taper off my methadone.
Dr. Belis Aladag: As quickly as I can tolerate
Dr. Belis Aladag: And then you ask them to work with you on a daily basis to lower it
Dr. Belis Aladag: You know, going down more than
Dr. Belis Aladag: A couple of milligrams. I mean, you could initially try to go down by like five milligrams at a time, and every couple of days. If you want or you could go weekly
Dr. Belis Aladag: No, but I mean it's a process and and you really need to like get to zero.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And then stay there, stay at zero for like four or five days before we try because the reason we want to wait that long is if we take it now, like let's say we gave it to today or Suboxone
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: You
Dr. Belis Aladag: Put yourself into withdrawal. The Suboxone activity is half of what methadone activity is and so methadone is on your receptors. Now, so if you kick that off and put the half reactivity Suboxone you're going to feel like, Oh my God, you know, I just wanted to Mega withdrawal.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Okay, I'm
Dr. Belis Aladag: Not gonna kill you. It's not like dangerous in that sense, but it feels bad.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah. Um, so I'd like to just do everything I can to get on the Suboxone as fast as possible. I wasn't even sure if I was going to end up going back to this methadone clinic.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Because I'm in really my I got in a car accident, a couple days ago. So now my transportation. The 45 minute drive it is to the Methadone clinic is really getting that little screwed up until I can get my car fixed anyway.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay. So you're thinking, Are you thinking, okay, I'll just stop, I'm not going to take anymore.
Yeah.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, so, but I'm okay. The thing is,
Dr. Belis Aladag: You may. We'll see how you do.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Like I said, I can give you. Clonidine patches. I'll give you the things that would help someone if we
Dr. Belis Aladag: weren't using Suboxone to help them through withdrawal. We have all the other things, right, like a muscle relaxer, do you get stomach pains stomach.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Cramps, I can give you
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Not much, not much.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, so maybe just the muscle relaxer the quantity and patch, just in general.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And then you have your clonazepam. I mean, it is it is a standard thing that you take anyway but it's there.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Between those three things, and you're not taking any more methadone. I mean, your body's going to clear itself of of the Methadone
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: And yeah.
To withdraw.
Dr. Belis Aladag: So you want to do like probably four or five days of that at least. And then, and then if you know you're feeling like I think it's, I don't know if we can try to start you on Suboxone
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Basically, like we could do a week, you know, meet again in a week and say okay and this week. Did you stay away from all opioids WHATSOEVER NO methadone know Suboxone, no nothing.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And if you have
Dr. Belis Aladag: Maybe we can try and then go from there.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay. The other option for you would be to be to go into an inpatient like you had in the past for that.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Situation go
Dr. Belis Aladag: Find an inpatient detox facility and tell them that you want to be induced onto Suboxone but you've been taking methadone and, most recently, you had 80 milligrams in your system.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And then they can induce you in the inpatient said setting, they could give you maybe more sedatives like phenobarbital, the heavy duty stuff to kind of keep your body calmer and stuff they can do it in that setting as well.
Dr. Belis Aladag: So those
Dr. Belis Aladag: Are crazy and you're like, this is too hard. I don't think I can do this, you know, that might be honestly the safest easiest way to try to do it. It's monitored.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Do you so you understand that.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, okay. Yeah, I'd like to do, we can to avoid that situation that just, I just don't like the idea of being, you know, away from everything you know
Dr. Belis Aladag: Yeah yeah
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay. I mean, we'll try no promises, though I mean like if anything you don't feel right about anything you can go, you know, obviously there's emergency room services if it's horrible, but
Dr. Belis Aladag: They're really the best places in inpatient detox. So you may want to still do the research, like call if your medical
Dr. Belis Aladag: There, there is that number, the sap see number do you have that number. There's a number where you call and they triage you and they can see like, okay, you're, you're, you need detox. So here's the detox center that's covered under your insurance or something.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, I've been doing a detox before I'm
Dr. Belis Aladag: Not aware, it is close to
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah yeah
Okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, so you have that as your like Plan B have it on the thing, just like, Hey, worst case scenario, just go there and like check in and tell them hey I'm switching please switch Mina Suboxone
Dr. Belis Aladag: That's what I do. I'm not just detoxing I'm detoxing from methadone getting on Suboxone that you got to tell them that piece.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Yeah, otherwise they put you on some automatic protocol on your on the street and you have no Suboxone
Yeah.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay. Okay, so let's do this. So I'm going to give you the medications necessary to hold you over and then we meet again in a week, we'll meet individually, because this is a unique situation. And then we see how you feel, like, how did it go. Are you okay
Dr. Belis Aladag: See if we want to attempt the induction.
Dr. Belis Aladag: You have any support at home, who do you live with.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, I live with my parents are very supportive. Yeah. So, okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Your parents. Okay, good. Any family history of substance use problems alcohol.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, a little bit of alcohol is no I'm on side, but she stopped drinking so
Dr. Belis Aladag: He did. Okay, good. That's good. Um, and then any surgeries. You've had
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: No, no.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Any history of suicidal thoughts ideation like attempts anything
Dr. Belis Aladag: Right now, we should worry about
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: No, no.
Dr. Belis Aladag: How about allergies to mess.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: No, no allergies.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Chart.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, no allergies and then how about nicotine you smoke or, or, yeah.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: I smoke probably like 10 cigarettes a day.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, so like half a pack a day.
Dr. Belis Aladag: You know, right now is probably not the best time to talk about quitting. But when you're ready, like we could do stuff for that too. We have patches. We can give you patches plus lozenge gum, you know, whatever.
We can work on
Dr. Belis Aladag: But right now.
Dr. Belis Aladag: We got a bigger
Issue.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And then you tell talk, talk to me about 15 years old is when you started was it with pills like what
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Well, yeah, it was like pills, you know, just
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: recreationally you know like oxy cotton and all that and then
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, it was mainly just the bills. You know, I'm sure for bills, not for me. I never really had a you know a reason to be prescribed it but I'm just getting it off the streets.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Gotcha, gotcha. Okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Do you use any other drugs anymore.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, I mean not recently in the past few days I've used marijuana because just, you know, something to get
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Something to me feeling a little bit better. Anyway, but I'm not much
Dr. Belis Aladag: Not much. Okay. Okay. Um,
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: But I don't like the idea of being on the methadone, it's so easy to diverge from the treatment plan like
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: When you're on Suboxone it's you can't really go out and take any opiates because they don't really have an effect. And let's take them certain amount
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: But with methadone, you can easily take something else and it, you know. So I think I like being on the spot on, it's a lot safer in that aspect.
Dr. Belis Aladag: It's true.
Dr. Belis Aladag: You're right, it has a stronger binding to the receptor. So if you try to use. It's not very effective.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Yeah um vs methadone is a full agonist. And yeah, people do unfortunately still use, you know, they chip or whatever, you know,
Yeah.
Dr. Belis Aladag: So either way, though, you know,
Dr. Belis Aladag: It's about where you're at, mentally, right, like, well, how far you allow yourself to go and having your own sense of like, okay, why am I even doing this in the first place. I'm taking this medication like I might as well follow through and do what I'm supposed to be doing.
Yeah.
Dr. Belis Aladag: But, yeah, yeah. There are some differences there, and also lifestyle wise you know like having a medication that like any other that you can take in your own privacy versus having to go somewhere.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Right, that's like you said 45 minute drive. I mean,
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, it'd be a lot easier to be the head of our firm, a new them the hills. So it's kind of like over by like Berryessa so it's kind of hard to get places, especially now that I'm waiting for my part of your paradigm, not even sure how long that's going to be
Dr. Belis Aladag: Oh man, I can't believe I'm sorry about the car accident. What happened there.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Is some she just stopped in the middle of the intersection, because it's something else going on. And I ended up hitting her in the back.
Huh.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Sorry about that. It's like
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: That's all right.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: So I'm putting in
Dr. Belis Aladag: Your prescriptions, as we're doing this.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Okay, and then I guess I'll just go to my regular pharmacy then right
Dr. Belis Aladag: What I have here is far Mocha integrative is that
Dr. Belis Aladag: Perfect, yeah. Yeah. So I'm putting in your clonazepam
Dr. Belis Aladag: I'm
Dr. Belis Aladag: Like I said, I'll put in a week's worth and and I'm going to put in a request that the team at the virtual clinic where you checked in that they help you get an appointment with our psychiatry team here.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And then establish care right
Dr. Belis Aladag: You can instigate that too, though. Just a call them. So after you and I hang up. You can call them and say, Okay, I need an appointment with her in one week and I also this week, I need to establish care with your psychiatrist. Sorry.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Okay.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, that's good. I wasn't sure if this is just going to be the, you know, able to handle just like the Suboxone or as an able be able to get everything to your
Dr. Belis Aladag: Ya know, we can we can we should be able to help you with everything so you don't have to keep having piecemeal
Yeah.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: All right, good.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And you're not on any other medication right now.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: We I am I also take effect stir and Abilify and
Dr. Belis Aladag: DO YOU HAVE THOSE ARE YOU OUT OF THOSE TWO
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: No, I have them. Thankfully, yeah. I've got my effects are Abilify and gabapentin
Okay, yeah.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: I have refills for all those two at the moment, but I'm
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Let me know if you need the dosages
Dr. Belis Aladag: Hold on, let me
Dr. Belis Aladag: I might. Hold on one sec. Okay.
Okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: OK, so I sent that in
Dr. Belis Aladag: In good
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, so that's in. I'm going to give you, nor can nor can is a nasal spray. If you overdose. Your parents find you. They you're not moving. You're not responding. They can spray this in your nose. It reverses an
Dr. Belis Aladag: opioid overdose, but it's temporary so they still need to call 911 and get you connected
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Okay, I actually have a good amount in our can right now, but we can always send it over to the pharmacy just, I mean,
Dr. Belis Aladag: You don't have to pick it up, then yeah yeah
Okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, and then it was like, Oh, I'm on a regular basis. Do you have any complaints like chest pain, shortness of breath fevers, chills, I don't know any any general system problems.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: You mean like
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: When I'm not taking this Suboxone or methadone.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Just on a day to day basis. Do you have any health
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Issues. Oh, not really. I mean, a lot of anxiety and
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: You know, some depression but that's about it.
Okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Um, you're not abuse bar anymore. You use
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Oh yeah, I've used bar. Yes, I am zombies are you
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, so I see abuse bar. This is coming from the pharmacy.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay thing. Okay, so there's abuse far 30
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Mm hmm.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And then there's, um,
Dr. Belis Aladag: You mentioned, what did you mention effects are Abilify
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: vilify and the gap event.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And it's all mainly for depression and anxiety, you have both.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Yeah, okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: I see you are given a muscle relaxer back in the day, so you know about that. The method.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Is that hopefully you want more of that during the
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Full um I've also had Soma when the pain really got to be pretty bad. And that was very helpful too.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Yeah, the only thing with that is it's, um, it's got a super sensitive quality which
Dr. Belis Aladag: You know, with everything.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: All your fans it up too much.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: You know, at least. Don't worry about me driving now anyway but
Dr. Belis Aladag: That's good. Right, I guess. Okay, so you have your Effects, or effects. There's 150
Dr. Belis Aladag: Yeah, okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: I got. Okay, so I got Gabba Penton view spar and effect, sir.
Dr. Belis Aladag: OK.
Dr. Belis Aladag: OK, so I'm
In Abilify
Dr. Belis Aladag: Oh, in the Abilify
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, it's just five milligrams
Dr. Belis Aladag: Has that helped. Did they added later on.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, you really don't notice it much. I don't think you know there's been times when I had run out and I just kind of pick it up from the pharmacy. I really never noticed much
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: It so I do notice the
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: The effects are
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Getting you know I ran out. It's just terrible and
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: So I think it's pretty awful.
Okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, sorry. Got it. Okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And save and close. Okay, so we'll get you that
Yeah.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, so we have a plan.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Tell me what the plan is. So I know you understand
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: So when I'm done here. I'm going to call the number back just to set up an appointment with you in a week and
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Then in a week. That would be with going without any methadone and just the other prescriptions. So then, yeah, in a week. We're an awfully start the Suboxone and
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Yeah, so I'm also going to see the psychiatrists, that's going to be with you guys on the talk to her. The receptionist begin with him or her also to continue the other psychotropic medications.
Hmm.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Exactly. Okay. Good. You got it. Yeah, I'm okay. I'm putting in also the quantity and patch. I'm giving you the higher, there's a point one and a point to give you a point to. I think it works well if you feel light headed, you could
Dr. Belis Aladag: Take it off or put your feet up, drink some water. It's a blood pressure lowering medication. So if you get lightheaded. That's why.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Yeah.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: But it's already in the tablets before never just never patched but
Yeah.
Dr. Belis Aladag: They're helpful right yeah really helpful. Back in the day, that was all we had. And it would help people get through withdrawal.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Oh, so I'll say use one patch on clean, dry skin per week.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, so like it's a week long patch.
Dr. Belis Aladag: So if you do take it off for brief whatever you can put it back on.
Dr. Belis Aladag: So I'll give you, I'll give you four. I think it comes at a four things. So it's a whole month's worth if you needed it, but you're not hopefully going to need it more than just this week and
Yeah.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: That okay so we got that ordered as well. And then I'll do the I'll do the muscle relaxer, not the summer, but the metal carbon wall.
Yeah.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And that's it. And then, so you've good so we're good.
Dr. Belis Aladag: And then moving forward. Once we get you stabilize we'll talk about. Okay, group format. Are you comfortable with groups like can we do check medical checking in a group thing and stuff, we can work on those things later.
Dr. Belis Aladag: I'm just concerned. Let's get you on switch from methadone to Suboxone so
Dr. Belis Aladag: Yeah, just, you know, you got to buckle down you you just mentally know it's going to be a hard time, you need to have your contingency plan of, like, okay, maybe I just need to go to the detox unit.
Dr. Belis Aladag: You need to have all your medications with you like the supportive medications and then just have your parents on board, knowing what you're doing, like, Hey, I'm transitioning. So this week. It's going to be a withdrawal like getting off of this
Dr. Belis Aladag: long acting opioids called methadone, it's, it's a process.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay. Cool. Any questions for me.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Um, I don't think so. No.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, awesome. Okay. Calvin. Um, I don't know if I forgot to ask anything else but we'll meet again soon in a week and we can always fill in the gaps, then
Dr. Belis Aladag: And are you working right now. I mean, you said you're
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Not working at the moment, sir.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, good. So you're at home. Okay. Okay, good. Oh, one on one therapy sessions are also available to
Dr. Belis Aladag: You can also set that up, it might be helpful.
Dr. Belis Aladag: I mean to have somebody to talk to. You know, just get things out. So one asked for the psychiatrists that can help you with medication.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Continuing, and then also you can say, hey, I also
Dr. Belis Aladag: Want to set it up with my therapist to assign therapist.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: Sure, yeah.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Okay, God, I will see you in a week.
Dr. Belis Aladag: Take good, okay.
“iMyFone”的 iPhone: All right. Thank